第 2 章：词语连读和分组。把词连起来说。
Chapter 2. Word Linking and Phrasing. Run your words together. As mentioned in the
正如上一章所说，在美国英语中，单词不是一个一个单独发音的。
previous chapter, in American English, words are not pronounced one by one.
通常，一个词的词尾会贴到下一个词的开头。
Usually, the end-of-one word attaches to the beginning of the next word. This is
这同样适用于首字母、数字和拼写；句子之间也有一种“黏合剂”。
also true for initials, numbers, and spelling. Part of the glue that connects
这种黏合剂是底层持续的嗡鸣或拖音，通常只在句号处断开。
sentences is an underlying hum or drone that only breaks when you come to a period
有时甚至句号处也不断。你的母语里也有这种底层嗡鸣。
and sometimes not even then. You have this underlying hum in your own language, and
它能大大帮助你听起来像母语者。先要掌握强语调。
it helps a great deal toward making you sound like a native speaker. Once you have
接着，把所有阶梯连接起来，让句子连成整体。
a strong intonation, you need to connect all those stair steps together so that
这样每句话都会听起来像一个很长的词；本章会讲词与词的连接。
each sentence sounds like one long word. This chapter is going to introduce you to
这些连接让我们按声音组说话，
the idea of liaisons, the connections between words, which allow us to speak in
而不是按一个个孤立的单词来听。
sound groups rather than in individual words. Just as we went over where to put
之前我们讲过语调放在哪里；这里要学习如何连接单词。
intonation, here you're going to learn how to connect words. Once you learn to use this
学会这个技巧后，你就能从这本练习书顺利迁移到其他材料，
technique, you can make the important leap from this practice book to other materials
为了让你更容易阅读，
in your own conversation. To make it easier for you to read, liaisons are
连读会这样标出来：They tell me that I'm easier。也可以写成 they
written like this. They tell me that I'm easier to understand. It could also be written, they
告诉我，我更容易被听懂了，但那样读起来太难。
tell me that I'm easier to understand, but it would be too hard to read.